<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<examples>
  <example>
    <code>Remove-EC2DiskImage -ConversionTaskId "import-i-123456"</code>
    <description>This example deletes the image file artifacts previously uploaded to Amazon S3 and used for the conversion with task ID 'import-i-123456'.  You are prompted for confirmation before the cmdlet proceeds. If the conversion is still in progress the cmdlet will issue an error message and cancel the deletion operation.</description>
  </example>
  <example>
    <code>Remove-EC2DiskImage -ConversionTaskId "import-i-123456" -IgnoreActiveTask</code>
    <description>This example deletes the image file artifacts previously uploaded to Amazon S3 and used for the conversion with task ID 'import-i-123456'.  You are prompted for confirmation before the cmdlet proceeds. The deletion proceeds even if the conversion task is still active.</description>
  </example>
  <example>
    <code>Remove-EC2DiskImage -ConversionTaskId "import-i-123456" -IgnoreActiveTask -Force</code>
    <description>This example deletes the image file artifacts previously uploaded to Amazon S3 and used for the conversion with task ID 'import-i-123456'.  You are not prompted for confirmation before the cmdlet proceeds. The deletion proceeds even if the conversion task is still active.</description>
  </example>
  <example>
    <code>Remove-EC2DiskImage -ConversionTaskId @("import-i-123456", "import-i-654321")</code>
    <description>This example deletes the image file artifacts previously uploaded to Amazon S3 and used for the specified conversion tasks. You are prompted for confirmation before the cmdlet proceeds. Because the -IgnoreActiveTask switch was not specified the deletion process will halt with an error on the first task it encounters that is still active.</description>
  </example>
  <example>
    <code>Remove-EC2DiskImage -ManifestUrl "https://myimages.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/windows2012.volume1/85512d11-89e0-4129-a638-9bd730451f37/windows2012-disk1.vmdkmanifest.xml?AWSAccessKeyId=MYACCESSKEYID..."</code>
    <description>This example deletes the image file artifacts associated with a conversion using the presigned url to the import manifest file in Amazon S3. No check is performed to verify that a conversion task is still active and using the artifacts but you are prompted for confirmation before proceeding. Add the -Force switch to suppress confirmation. An array of manifest urls can be supplied to the -ManifestUrl parameter.</description>
  </example>
  <example>
    <code>Remove-EC2DiskImage -BucketName "myimages" -ManifestFileKey "windows2012.volume1/85512d11-89e0-4129-a638-9bd730451f37/windows2012-disk1.vmdkmanifest.xml"</code>
    <description>This example deletes the image file artifacts associated with a conversion by using the name of the bucket containing the artifacts and the Amazon S3 object key of the import manifest file that was created by the Import-EC2Instance or Import-EC2Volume cmdlets. No check is performed to verify that a conversion task is still active and using the artifacts but you are prompted for confirmation before proceeding. Add the -Force switch to suppress confirmation. This format is useful for deleting artifacts if an error is reported by the Import-EC2Instance or Import-EC2Volume cmdlets - in these scenarios the value required for the -ManifestFileKey parameter is included in the error message that they display. An array of keys can be passed to the -ManifestFileKey parameter.</description>
  </example>
</examples>